Crystal Payne Johnson

Dallas, TX | 214-995-8497 | cpaynejohnson@gmail.com | linkedin.com/in/cpaynejohnson

PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

Experienced technical support representative with strong analytical and problem-solving abilities. Able to achieve objectives under challenging circumstances. Brings a logical and resourceful approach to problem-solving. Excited to share my proven skills and customer centric attitude.

SKILLS

- Troubleshooting
- Windows 8/10
- Positive Attitude

- Phone/Email Support
- Active Directory
- Active Listening

- Microsoft Office
- Attention to Detail
- Working Remotely

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

IT Support Coordinator, Gold's Gym

10/2023 - present

Provide identity and access management to over 2,500 US employees, including onboarding, transfers and offboarding.

- Receive requests via ServiceDesk Plus to provision employee profiles in Active Directory, including creating, updating and removing permissions and user accounts.
- Create and update profiles in Motionsoft.
- Run a script to create email accounts. Use O365 to update email permissions.
- Use ServiceDesk Plus ticketing system to track and address issues submitted by users.

Apprentice - Technology Strategy, Verizon

11/2021 - 11/2022

Worked with an Agile product management team on a multi-year strategic project aiming to modernize the Adobe Experience Manager (AEM) content management platform.

- Created and managed Jira tickets to track tasks with external team dependencies.
- Assisted with daily scrum calls and managing the product backlog while following the Agile framework.
- Composed daily communications for globally distributed teammates, external teams and stakeholders to maintain team productivity and knowledge of project status.
- Assisted with creating documents and presentations for management.

Digital Experience Coordinator, Gold's Gym

5/2020 - 11/2021

Provided technical support for Gold's mobile applications via email to over 20,000 members and over 5,000 US employees.

- Created and updated employee and member profiles in Motionsoft and MotionVibe systems, also unlocked accounts and updated passwords for access to company apps.
- Resolved issues encountered with Gold's mobile applications via email and Fresh Desk tickets.
- Educated users on features of apps.
- Worked cross functionally to resolve reported software bugs and other app issues.

• Processed refunds via Google Play Store.

IT Support Coordinator, Gold's Gym

6/2019 - 4/2020

Provided identity and access management to over 5,000 US employees, including onboarding, transfers and offboarding.

- Received requests via Service Now to provision employee profiles in Active Directory, including creating, updating and removing permissions and user accounts.
- Processed an average of 75 identity access requests per day.
- Created and updated profiles in Motionsoft.
- Ran a script to create email accounts. Used O365 to update email permissions.
- Used Service Now ticketing system to track and address issues submitted by users.

Planned Career Break

2/2017 - 5/2019

An intentional pause to focus on family and education.

- Provided full time caregiving.
- Attended Western Governors University full time.

Help Desk Analyst I, Robert Half

3/2016 - 1/2017

Provided technical support in person and by phone to over 2,000 US employees.

- Assisted an average of 65 customers each day and maintained 82.7% first call resolution rate.
- Used Active Directory to reset passwords, unlock user accounts, deprovision accounts, add users to security groups and adjust mail flow settings.
- Assisted employees with Microsoft Office applications, troubleshot PCs, laptops, network and VPN connectivity issues, also installed and troubleshot networked printers.
- Used Remote Assistance and SCCM to remotely troubleshoot networked PCs, laptops and thin clients.
- Troubleshot Airwatch installations on iOS and Android phones.

CERTIFICATIONS

Microsoft Security, CompTIA Network+ GIAC GFACT Compliance and Identity CompTIA Security+ GIAC GSEC

Fundamentals Cisco CyberOps Associate GIAC GCIH (in progress)

EDUCATION

Associate of Science in Computer Information Systems

Delgado Community College, New Orleans, LA

12/1994

Completed 103 hours of coursework towards:

Bachelor of Science in Network Operations and Security

Western Governors University, Salt Lake City, UT

11/16 - 4/19